Guide to the W.S.U. Lantern Slides 1892-1944
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 6: Pullman Scenes
  - Palouse River - Pullman, undated (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - Pullman from Campus, undated (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - Pullman in Winter, undated (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - Blalock Fruit Farm, undated; With duplicate negative (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - Women Riding in Buggy, undated (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - Looking West on Main Street, undated (Box 4, Folder 374a)
- Series 7: Landscapes
  - Cloud Cap Inn - Mt. Adams in Distance, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - Mt. Adams from Yakima Peak, undated (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - Mt. Baker from saddle of Mt. Herman, 1924; Color tinted (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - Easton Glacier - Mt. Baker, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 378)
  - Mt. Baker looking North from Glacier Peak, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - Mt. Baker, Easton glacier, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 380)
  - Mt. Baker, Sherman Peak, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - Mt. Baker, Black Butte, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - Mt. Baker summit, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - Mt. Baker and Mazama Dome, from between Table Mt. and Mt. Herman, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - Mt. Baker from Twin Lakes, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - Mt. Baker from Artists Point near Austin Pass, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - Mt. Baker from Baker Lake, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - Blue Glacier, Mt. Olympus, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - Blue Glacier, Mt. Olympus, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 389)
  - Lake Blanca and Columbia Glacier, undated (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - Lake Blanca, undated (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - Lake Blanca and Columbia Glacier, undated (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - Lake Blanca, undated (Box 5, Folder 393)
  - Lake Blanca and Columbia Glacier, undated (Box 5, Folder 394)
  - Alpine landscape near Lake Blanca, undated (Box 5, Folder 395)
  - Mountain landscape near Lake Blanca, undated (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - Alpine landscape near Lake Blanca, undated (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - Chelan River, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - Lake Chelan, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 399)
  - Lake Chelan, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 400)
  - Mt. Baker and Deming Glacier from Three Sisters mountains, OR, undated (Box 5, Folder 401)
  - Chelan Cascade, undated (Box 5, Folder 402)
  - Waterfall, Chelan Cascade, undated (Box 5, Folder 403)
  - Chelan Cascade, undated; Negative 89-038 (Box 5, Folder 404)
  - Glacier Peak, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 405)
  - Indian Head Peak, Chelan County, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 406)
  - Indian Head Peak, 1921; Negative 89-036 (Box 5, Folder 407)
  - Indian Pass (near Glacier Peak), 1921 (Box 5, Folder 408)
  - Indian Pass, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 409)
  - Glacier Peak from Indian Head Peak, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 410)
  - Glacier Peak from Indian Head Peak, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 411)
  - Glacier Peak, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 412)
  - Glacier Peak, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 413)
  - White Chuck River - Glacier Peak, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 414)
  - Three Fingers - North of Glacier Peak, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 415)
  - Ridge Near Glacier Peak, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 416)
  - Glacier Peak, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 417)
  - Glacier Peak, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 418)
  - View from White Church Trail, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 419)
  - Glacier Peak Summit, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 420)
  - Glacier Peak at 5500 ft. in elevation, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 420a)
  - Glacier Peak. Fir and Hemlock trees in foreground, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 421)
  - Glacier Peak at 5500 ft. in elevation, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 421a)
  - NNW Glacier Peak, 6000 ft. level, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 422)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 423)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 424)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 425)
  - Glacier Peak (?) glaciers, undated (Box 5, Folder 426)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 427)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 428)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 429)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 430)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 431)
  - Glacier Peak, undated (Box 5, Folder 432)
  - Grande Rhonde River Valley, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 433)
  - Mt. St. Helens, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 434)
  - Mount Saint Helens, 1925; Cracked (Box 5, Folder 435)
  - Mt. St. Helens, undated (Box 5, Folder 436)
  - Hoh River, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 437)
  - Mt. Hood, Oregon, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 438)
  - Mt. Hood, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 439)
  - Mt. Hood, Oregon - Government Camp, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 439a)
  - Mt. Hood, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 440)
  - Mt. Hood, 1926; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 441)
  - Mt. Hood. Caldera Wall, 1926; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 442)
  - Camp in Horseshoe Basin, undated (Box 5, Folder 443)
  - L Canyon, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 444)
  - Mill Creek Glacier, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 445)
  - Olympic Mountains, Canyon Creek burn, Deer Lake, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 446)
  - Olympic Mountains, Cat Creek, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 447)
  - Rainier National Park, 1923; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 448)
  - Paradise Valley - Rainier National Park, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 449)
  - Paradise Valley, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 450)
  - Rainier National Park pack train, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 451)
  - Tatoosh range from above Paradise Valley, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 452)
  - Mt. Rainier, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 453)
  - Mt. Rainier, 1923; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 454)
  - Mt. Rainier, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 455)
  - Mt. Rainier from Reflection Lake, 1923; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 456)
  - Cinnamon Phase of Black Bear - Rainier National Park, undated (Box 5, Folder 457)
  - Red Mountain, Whatcom Co., 1927; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 458)
  - Red Mountain, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 459)
  - Red Mountain, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 460)
  - Red Mountains from north of Glacier Peak, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 461)
  - Reynolds Peak, 1921. (Box 5, Folder 462)
  - Reynolds Peak, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 463)
  - Saddle Mountains from Priest Rapids, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 464)
  - Sawtooth Ridge, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 465)
  - 76 Basin, undated (Box 5, Folder 466)
  - 76 Basin, undated (Box 5, Folder 467)
  - 76 Basin, undated (Box 5, Folder 468)
  - 76 Basin, undated (Box 5, Folder 469)
  - 76 Basin, undated (Box 5, Folder 470)
  - 76 Basin, undated (Box 5, Folder 471)
  - Mount Shuksan, 1927; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 472)
  - Mt. Shuksan, 9037 ft., 1927; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 472a)
  - Mt. Shuksan, 1927; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 473)
  - Mt. Shuksan, 1924; Color tinted (Box 5, Folder 474)
  - Mt. Simcoe, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 475)
  - Up Skagit from Sourdough, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 476)
  - Missing (6/12/2019) (Box 5, Folder 477)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 478)
  - Snake River, undated; Negative 89-039 (Box 5, Folder 479)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 480)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 481)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 482)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 483)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 484)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 485)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 486)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 487)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 5, Folder 488)
  - Hells Canyon Rim, undated (Box 5, Folder 489)
  - Hells Canyon, undated (Box 5, Folder 490)
  - Lewiston Grade, undated (Box 6, Folder 491)
  - Table Mountain, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 492)
  - Table Mountain, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 493)
  - Three Sister, Oregon, undated (Box 6, Folder 494)
  - Three Sister, Oregon, undated (Box 6, Folder 495)
  - Twin Butte, Idaho, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 496)
  - Twin Butte, Selway National Forest, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 497)
  - Twin Butte, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 498)
  - Twin Butte, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 499)
  - Twin Lakes Region, 1927; Color tinted (Box 6, Folder 500)
  - Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 501)
  - Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 502)
  - Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 503)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 504)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 505)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 506)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 507)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 508)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 509)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 510)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 511)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 512)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 513)
  - Upper Twin Lakes, undated (Box 6, Folder 514)
  - Upper Twin Lakes - Monte Cristo District, undated (Box 6, Folder 515)
  - White Chuck River, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 516)
  - White Chuck River, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 517)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 518)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 519)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 520)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 521)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 522)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 523)
  - Alpine Lake, undated (Box 6, Folder 524)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 525)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 526)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 527)
  - Alpine Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 528)
  - Alpine Landscape. Silver Tip Mt. and Silver Lake in background, undated (Box 6, Folder 529)
  - Ice Formation, undated (Box 6, Folder 530)
  - Ice Formation, undated (Box 6, Folder 531)
  - Tepee and Log Cabin, undated (Box 6, Folder 532)
  - House in the Mountains, undated (Box 6, Folder 533)
  - Sheep Herd, undated (Box 6, Folder 534)
  - Bears in Garbage Dump, undated (Box 6, Folder 535)
  - Lunchtime, undated (Box 6, Folder 536)
  - People in National Park, undated (Box 6, Folder 537)
  - General Landscape: railroad bridge in scrub lands, undated (Box 6, Folder 538)
  - Native People of Greenland, undated (Box 6, Folder 539)
  - Agriculture and Fire Department Scenes, undated; Color tinted (Box 6, Folder 540)
- Series 8: Teaching Aids
  - Map: Mt. Baker National Forest, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 541)
  - Map: U.S. Vegetation Regions, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 542)
  - Map: Washington State, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 543)
  - Map: Region Affected by Spokane Floods, undated (Box 6, Folder 544)
  - Map: Washington State, undated (Box 6, Folder 545)
  - Map: World Sugar Production, undated (Box 6, Folder 546)
  - Map: World Cotton Production, undated (Box 6, Folder 547)
  - Map: World Rice Production, undated (Box 6, Folder 548)
  - Map: World Oats Production, undated (Box 6, Folder 549)
  - Map: World Potato Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 550)
  - Map: World Corn Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 551)
  - Map: World Wheat Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 552)
  - Map: World Population, undated (Box 6, Folder 553)
  - Map: World Coffee Production, undated (Box 6, Folder 554)
  - Map: India/Ceylon and Japan Rice Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 555)
  - Map: North America Plant Regions, undated (Box 6, Folder 556)
  - Map: U.S. Wheat Production, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 557)
  - Map: U.S. Hay and Forage Production, undated (Box 6, Folder 558)
  - Map: U.S. Apple Production, undated (Box 6, Folder 559)
  - Map: U.S. Oats Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 560)
  - Map: U.S. Corn Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 561)
  - Map: U.S. Sugar Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 562)
  - Map: U.S. Vegetable Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 563)
  - Map: U.S. Citrus Fruit Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 564)
  - Map: U.S. Grapevine Acreage, undated (Box 6, Folder 565)
  - Map: U.S. Horse Distribution, undated (Box 6, Folder 566)
  - Map: Early Pleistocene Continental and Glacier Boundaries, undated (Box 6, Folder 567)
  - Map: Hood River Topographic Quadrangle (USGS), undated (Box 6, Folder 568)
  - Map: Hood River Topographic Quadrangle (USGS), undated (Box 6, Folder 569)
  - Diagram: Geographic Geyser Profile, undated (Box 6, Folder 570)
  - Diagram: Profile of Mammoth Hot Springs, undated (Box 6, Folder 571)
  - Ecology Diagram, undated (Box 6, Folder 572)
  - Cereal Investigations - Wheat Stalks, undated (Box 6, Folder 573)
  - Cereal Investigations, undated (Box 6, Folder 574)
  - Cereal Investigations, undated (Box 6, Folder 575)
  - Cereals, undated (Box 6, Folder 576)
  - Wheat Plants, undated (Box 6, Folder 577)
  - Close up of Tree Stem, undated (Box 6, Folder 578)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 579)
  - Desert Landscape. Desert lake, undated (Box 6, Folder 580)
  - Desert Landscape. Canyon with waterfall, undated (Box 6, Folder 581)
  - Desert Landscape. Desert waterfall, undated (Box 6, Folder 582)
  - Desert Landscape. Desert waterfall, undated (Box 6, Folder 583)
  - Desert Landscape. Desert river valley, undated (Box 6, Folder 584)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 585)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 586)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 587)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 588)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 589)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 590)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 591)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 592)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 593)
  - Desert Landscape, undated (Box 6, Folder 594)
  - Scabland Vegetation, undated (Box 6, Folder 595)
  - Scablands, undated (Box 6, Folder 596)
  - Palouse Falls, undated (Box 6, Folder 597)
  - Palouse Falls, undated (Box 6, Folder 598)
  - Palouse Falls, undated (Box 6, Folder 599)
  - Palouse Falls, undated (Box 7, Folder 600)
  - Palouse Falls, undated (Box 7, Folder 601)
  - Palouse Falls, undated (Box 7, Folder 602)
  - Islands of Lower Columbia River, undated (Box 7, Folder 603)
  - Columbia River, undated (Box 7, Folder 604)
  - Columbia River, undated; Broken (Box 7, Folder 605)
  - Scablands, undated (Box 7, Folder 606)
  - The Dalles, Oregon, undated (Box 7, Folder 607)
  - Snake River, undated (Box 7, Folder 608)
  - Washington Range Land, undated (Box 7, Folder 609)
  - Grand Coulee, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 610)
  - Rockford, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 611)
  - Wenatchee, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 612)
  - Kennewick, WA, with tumbleweeds, undated (Box 7, Folder 613)
  - Palouse Falls, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 614)
  - Palouse Falls, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 615)
  - River Valley - Northern Palouse Country, undated (Box 7, Folder 616)
  - River Valley - Landscape, undated (Box 7, Folder 617)
  - Eastern Montana Badlands, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 618)
  - Palouse Country Landscape, undated (Box 7, Folder 619)
  - Palouse Country, undated (Box 7, Folder 620)
  - Palouse Hills, undated (Box 7, Folder 621)
  - Palouse Country, undated (Box 7, Folder 622)
  - Farm Landscape, undated (Box 7, Folder 623)
  - Palouse Country. Aspen and Cottonwood trees southeast of Pullman, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 624)
  - Willows Restraining Stream in Pullman, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 625)
  - Palouse Country, undated; Negative 87-516 (Box 7, Folder 626)
  - Palouse Country, undated (Box 7, Folder 627)
  - Palouse Country, undated (Box 7, Folder 628)
  - Palouse Country and Horse Drawn combine, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 629)
  - Palouse Country and Horse Drawn combine, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 630)
  - Palouse Country and Horse Drawn combine, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 631)
  - Horse Drawn Combine, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 632)
  - Horse Drawn Combine, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 633)
  - Horse Drawn Combine, undated (Box 7, Folder 634)
  - Tractor Drawn Combine, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 635)
  - Tractor Drawn Combine, undated (Box 7, Folder 636)
  - Tractor Drawn Combine, undated (Box 7, Folder 637)
  - Tractor Drawn Combine, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 638)
  - Tractor Drawn Combine, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 639)
  - Combine - Self Propelled, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 640)
  - Combine - Self Propelled, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 641)
  - Combine - Self Propelled, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 642)
  - Threshing Scene, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 643)
  - Palouse Hills, undated (Box 7, Folder 644)
  - Palouse Hills, undated (Box 7, Folder 645)
  - Palouse Country, undated; Negative 87-507 (Box 7, Folder 646)
  - Palouse River, North Fork, undated (Box 7, Folder 647)
  - Nebraska Steppe, undated (Box 7, Folder 648)
  - Rural Landscape, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 649)
  - Great Plains Landscape, Kansas, undated; Color tinted (Box 7, Folder 650)
  - Pasture/Forest Land, Beatrice, Indiana, undated (Box 7, Folder 651)
  - Reforestation, Indiana, undated (Box 7, Folder 652)
  - Eroded Hillsides, undated (Box 7, Folder 653)
  - Kettle Falls, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 654)
  - Kettle Falls, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 655)
  - Kettle Falls, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 656)
  - Kettle Falls, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 657)
  - Kettle Falls, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 658)
  - Kettle Falls, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 659)
  - Kettle Falls, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 660)
  - Preston Falls, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 661)
  - Bonny Lake, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 662)
  - Bonny Lake, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 663)
  - Bonny Lake, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 664)
  - Bonny Lake, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 665)
  - Bonny Lake, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 666)
  - Bonny Lake, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 667)
  - Bonny Lake, WA, undated (Box 7, Folder 668)
  - St. Joe National Forest, undated (Box 7, Folder 669)
  - Little North Fork of the Clearwater, undated (Box 7, Folder 670)
  - North Fork of Clearwater River, undated (Box 7, Folder 671)
  - Rocky Mt. Foothills, Montana, undated (Box 7, Folder 672)
  - Forest Road, undated (Box 7, Folder 673)
  - Forest Road, undated (Box 7, Folder 674)
  - Forest Trail, undated (Box 7, Folder 675)
  - Log Cabin Forest, undated (Box 7, Folder 676)
  - Forest Campsite, undated (Box 7, Folder 677)
  - Forest Landscape, undated (Box 7, Folder 678)
  - Forest Landscape, undated (Box 7, Folder 679)
  - Forest Landscape, undated (Box 7, Folder 680)
  - Forest Fire, undated (Box 7, Folder 681)
  - Men dwarfed by Trees, undated (Box 7, Folder 682)
  - Man overlooking Canyon, undated; Negative 89-035 (Box 7, Folder 683)
  - Mountain Gorge Bridge, undated (Box 7, Folder 684)
  - Drawing of Canyon, undated (Box 7, Folder 685)